Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Project Files
  - Subseries 3: Tongues Untied
    - Tongues Untied Controversy at Issue (Box 106, Folder 1)
      Paper given by Patricia Aufderheide at the International Communications Association Convention in Miami, 1992
    - Tongues Untied POV (Box 106, Folder 2)
      Controversy surrounding broadcast of Tongues Untied
    - Tongues Untied POV (Box 106, Folder 3)
      Articles surrounding controversy of airing/nonbroadcast of Tongues Untied
    - Tongues Untied Press packet (Box 106, Folder 4)
      Copies of publicity materials
    - Tongues Untied Press release (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Tongues Untied POV Reviews, originals (Box 106, Folder 6)
      Newspaper cuttings from various national and local papers from 1991 about Tongues Untied controversy
    - Tongues Untied photocopies of newspaper cuttings (Box 106, Folder 7)
      Various national and local papers from 1991 about Tongues Untied controversy
    - Tongues Untied Reviews, letters of support, newspaper articles (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Tongues Untied POV Reviews, originals (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Tongues Untied POV Letters of support, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Tongues Untied Poems (Box 107, Folder 1)
      Photocopies of poems by Essex Hemphill and Alan Miller
    - Tongues Untied (Box 107, Folder 2)
      Reginald T Jackson - transcript of interview
    - Tongues Untied POV/PBS (Box 107, Folder 3)
      reviews and Correspondence, 1991
    - Tongues Untied POV Reviews, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      Photocopies of press reaction to Tongues Untied controversy
    - Tongues Untied POV Reviews 1, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Tongues Untied POV Reviews 2, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      Newspaper cuttings of press reaction to Tongues Untied controversy
    - Tongues Untied POV station letters and responses (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Tongues Untied POV viewer comments (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Tongues Untied POV viewer comments (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Tongues Untied Swedish Television screening Correspondence (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Tongues Untied University of Minnesota Press (Box 107, Folder 11)
      Correspondence about publishing rights for script of Tongues Untied
    - Tongues Untied Western States grant agreement, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Tongues Untied Whitney Bi-ennial Video exhibition (Box 107, Folder 13)
      Correspondence, 1991
    - Tongues Untied Grant agreement, FAF, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Tongues Untied Research Articles (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Tongues Untied Research Articles (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Tongues Untied Research Articles (Box 108, Folder 4)
      Newspaper cuttings, 1988/89
    - Tongues Untied Research Articles - Magazines (Box 108, Folder 5)
      Changing Men, Black Film Review and The Space
    - Tongues Untied Articles about Riggs and Tongues (Box 108, Folder 6)
      Photocopies
    - Tongues Untied PBS - A Guide to Crisis Management (Box 108, Folder 7)
      Tongues Untied is mentioned
    - Tongues Untied Clips Packet, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Tongues Untied Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Tongues Untied Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Tongues Untied Awards (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Tongues Untied Berlin Film festival, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Tongues Untied British Film Institute Correspondence, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Tongues Untied Cable broadcast Correspondence, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Tongues Untied Christian Coalition fax, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Tongues Untied Contracts - Frameline (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Tongues Untied Contracts - KCET (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Tongues Untied Contracts - WNET (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Tongues Untied Correspondence - POV (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Tongues Untied Contact List (Box 109, Folder 10)
      Includes performers information and 'Other Countries' performance information
    - Tongues Untied Credits and end titles (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Tongues Untied Distribution details (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Tongues Untied Distribution - Frameline (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Tongues Untied Edit Decision Lists and Production Notes (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Tongues Untied Essays about Tongues Untied (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Tongues Untied Funding - Chicago Resource Center (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Tongues Untied Funding - FAF Grant (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - London (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Brochures from screenings (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Lesbian and Gay Festivals (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Screenings (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Screenings/Correspondence for screenings (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Film Festival programmes (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Tongues Untied Festivals - Film Festival programmes (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Tongues Untied Buchanan Controversy (Box 110, Folder 6)
      Newspaper cuttings
    - Tongues Untied Buchanan Controversy (Box 110, Folder 7)
      Faxes from the press
    - Tongues Untied Buchanan Controversy (Box 110, Folder 8)
      Correspondence
    - Tongues Untied Buchanan Controversy (Box 110, Folder 9)
      NY Times article fax photocopy
    - Tongues Untied Invoices (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Tongues Untied Income (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Tongues Untied KQED Contract (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Tongues Untied Tape Logs (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Photocopied reviews and newspaper articles - Tongues Untied (Flat-box 215, Folder 11)
    - Tongues Untied Screening Postcard, 2004, - 'Marlon Riggs Ten Years after' (Half-box 219, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of Participation, Film Arts Festival - Tongues Untied 1989 and Affirmations 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 7)
    - Berlin Film Festival award to Tongues Untied, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 8)
    - Wellington Film festival award to Tongues Untied, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 9)
    - Certificate of Merit to Tongues Untied, Big Muddy Film Festival, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 10)
    - D.C. International Film Festival award to Tongues Untied, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 11)
    - Cleveland International Film Festival award to Tongues Untied, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 12)
    - Special Jury Award of the USA Film Festival, Dallas to Tongues Untied, 1990 (Flat-box 226, Folder 13)
    - Newark Black Film Festival Award to Riggs for Tongues Untied, 1991 (Flat-box 226, Folder 16)
    - Prized Pieces Annual International Video and Film Award, 1990 (Flat-box 228)
      Runner Up Cultural Affairs Documentary to Riggs for Tongues Untied from the National Black Programming Consortium
    - Prized Pieces Annual International Video and Film Award Winner, 1990 (Flat-box 228)
      Best Black Independent Producer Award to Riggs for Tongues Untied from the National Black Programming Consortium
    - National Educational Film and Video Festival (Flat-box 229)
      Gold Apple Award to Tongues Untied, 1990
  - Subseries 4: Affirmations
    - Project Papers: Affirmations, includes floppy discs (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Affirmations Awards, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Affirmations Frameline contract (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Affirmations Script (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Affirmations WNET agreement, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Affirmations Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Affirmations Credits (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Affirmations EDL (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Affirmations Photos (Box 88, Folder 8)
      Photo of Reginald T. Jackson in Affirmations
    - Affirmations Screenings, 1990-91 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 5: Color Adjustment
    - Color Adjustment Note cards with quoted selections from interviews (Box 9)
      Interviews with Bruce Paltrow, Herman Grey, Norman Lear, Pat Turner, Esther Rolle, Alvin Poussaint, David Wolper, Steve Bochco, Henry Gates, Denise Nicholls, Tim Reid, Bob Henry, Hal Kanter, Diahann Carroll and Sheldon Leonard.
    - Color Adjustment Notes on the Greenwood Story (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Color Adjustment lists of onscreen credits and graphics (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Color Adjustment Transcript (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Color Adjustment selection of notes (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment lists (Box 10, Folder 5)
      5inch floppy discs with box 93
    - Color Adjustment printed list of time codes (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Research material for Color Adjustment - black life and TV shows
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings on black life and TV shows (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Research material for Color Adjustment
    - Transcript of interview with Pat Turner (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Transcript of interview with Henry Gates (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Transcript of interview with Alvin Poussaint (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Transcript of interview with Norman Lear (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Transcript of interview with Tim and Daphne Reid (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Transcript of interview with Steve Bochco (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Transcript of interview with David Wolper (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Transcript of interview with Herman Gray (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Transcript of interview with Bruce Paltrow (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Transcript of interview with Hal Kanter (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Transcript of interview with Bob Henry (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Transcript of interview with Sheldon Leonard (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Transcript of interview with Denise Nicholls (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Transcript of interview with Esther Rolles (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Time codes for Interview tapes (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Transcript of interview with Diahann Carroll (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Pencil highlighted areas and time codes for use in program
    - Transcript of interview with Pat Turner (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Transcript of interview with Henry Gates (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Transcript of interview with Alvin Poussaint (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Transcript of interview with Norman Lear (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Transcript of interview with Tim and Daphne Reid (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Transcript of interview with Steve Bochco (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Transcript of interview with David Wolper (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Transcript of interview with Herman Gray (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Mixing logs for Color Adjustment (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Photocopies of mixing logs for Color Adjustment (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Audio Mixing logs for Color Adjustment (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Transcript of interview with Bruce Paltrow (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Transcript of interview with Hal Kanter (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Transcript of interview with Bob Henry (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Transcript of interview with Sheldon Leonard (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Transcript of interview with Denise Nicholls (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Transcript of interview with Esther Rolles (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 45, Folder 3)
      Color Adjustment and Tongues Untied showings from around the country, 1992
    - Photocopies and faxes of newspaper and magazine articles and clippings (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Color adjustment screenings, 1992
    - Color Adjustment Agreement with the American Documentary Inc, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Color Adjustment Correspondence with the Chicago Defender for articles used, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Color Adjustment Documentary Proposal (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Color Adjustment Awards achieved, information and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment Awards application for the DuPont award, Columbia University, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Color Adjustment Bank account/General Fund - Invoices, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Color Adjustment Bank Account, Citibank statements, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Color Adjustment Bank Account, Citibank statements, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment Bank Account/General Fund, Invoices Paid, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Budget/Saundra's bookkeeping, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Color Adjustment Budget, by funders, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Color Adjustment Correspondence with the BBC, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Color Adjustment Information about consultants (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Color Adjustment Consultants - Herman Gray (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment Consultants - Fred MacDonald (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Color Adjustment Consultants - Pat Turner (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Color Adjustment Production - Personnel (Resume) (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Color Adjustment Consultants - Mary Ann Watson (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright letters, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Color Adjustment California Newsreel contracts (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Color Adjustment California Newsreel notes and script (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Color Adjustment California Newsreel Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Color Adjustment Captioning (Box 78, Folder 23)
      Information from the National Captioning Institute
    - Color Adjustment Credits (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Color Adjustment Evaluations from screening (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Master List (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Eddie Anderson (Box 79, Folder 2)
      Correspondence about Jack Benny Clip
    - Color Adjustment Copyright (Box 79, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Archive Films
    - Color Adjustment Copyright (Box 79, Folder 4)
      Arena Associates (Clip from 'The Lieutenant')
    - Color Adjustment Copyright (Box 79, Folder 5)
      Ray Atherton (Beulah clips)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright (Box 79, Folder 6)
      Mike Avery (Amos n Andy Clips)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright (Box 79, Folder 7)
      St Martins Press (Baldwin quotes)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Milton Berle (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Budget Films Stock Footage (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - CBS TV (Box 79, Folder 10)
      Amos n Andy
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Carsey Warner Productions (Box 79, Folder 11)
      Cosby Show/Different World
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - CBS News Archive (Box 79, Folder 12)
      Civil Rights footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Columbia Pictures Television (Box 79, Folder 13)
      All in the Family/Good Times
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Ethnic Notions clips used in Color Adjustment (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Ernie Fosselius (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Fox News Archive (Box 79, Folder 16)
      News Clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Fox Television (Box 79, Folder 17)
      Julia footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Grinberg Film Libraries (Box 79, Folder 18)
      News and Stock Footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Group W Productions (Box 79, Folder 19)
      David Frost/Diahann Carroll interview
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Harvard Theatre Collection (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Timothy Keir (Beulah) (Box 79, Folder 21)
      Beulah footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - KPIX (Box 79, Folder 22)
      MLK/Black Panther Rally footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - KRON (Box 79, Folder 23)
      Strike/Oakland clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - KQED (Box 79, Folder 24)
      Various shots of Berkeley/Oakland
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - KTVU (Box 79, Folder 25)
      Panthers Clip
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Stephen Lighthill (Box 79, Folder 26)
      SNCC Rally footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Library of Congress (Various clips) (Box 79, Folder 27)
      Various clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - MCA International (Box 79, Folder 28)
      Jack Benny Show
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - MGM Pathe (Box 79, Folder 29)
      East Side West Side
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Fred MacDonald (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Mississippi State Archive (Box 79, Folder 31)
      Newsfilm
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - MTM Productions (Box 79, Folder 32)
      Hill St Blues
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - NBC News Archive (Box 80, Folder 1)
      Various news clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - National Archives (Box 80, Folder 2)
      TV watching clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - National Museum of American History (Box 80, Folder 3)
      Mammy Clip from Ethnic Notions
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - New York Times (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Original FilmVideo Library (Box 80, Folder 5)
      TV shows footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Paramount Television (Box 80, Folder 6)
      Defenders footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Petrified Films (Box 80, Folder 7)
      TV ads/watching TV footage clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Harvey Richards Film Collection (Box 80, Folder 8)
      Rally/1960s demonstrations footage clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Robert Rose (Box 80, Folder 9)
      Burning flag shots
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - ShokusVideo (Box 80, Folder 10)
      TV commercials/shows
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Danny Thomas (Box 80, Folder 11)
      Texaco star theatre footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - 3F Productions (Box 80, Folder 12)
      ISpy footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - UCLA Film Archive (Box 80, Folder 13)
      Integration footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Viacom (Box 80, Folder 14)
      Franks Place
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Video Resources/Ira Gallen (Box 80, Folder 15)
      TV Commercials
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Video Yesteryear (Box 80, Folder 16)
      TV Show clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Warner Bros. Television (Box 80, Folder 17)
      Roots footage
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - David Loeb Weiss (Box 80, Folder 18)
      Vietnam protest clip
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - WHDH-TV Boston (Box 80, Folder 19)
      Anti-bussing clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - Worldvision Enterprises (Box 80, Folder 20)
      Mod Squad clips
    - Color Adjustment Copyright - WTN (Box 80, Folder 21)
      Watts Riots footage
    - Color Adjustment Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 22)
      Various letters and enquiries, 1990-92
    - Color Adjustment Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 23)
      Peabody Award, 1992/3
    - Color Adjustment American Experience (Box 80, Folder 24)
      Distribution
    - Color Adjustment Icarus Films (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Color Adjustment Icarus Films (Box 80, Folder 26)
      International Distribution
    - Color Adjustment Icarus Films (Box 80, Folder 27)
      Distribution - French Edits
    - Color Adjustment Icarus Films (Box 80, Folder 28)
      Distribution - French TV
    - Color Adjustment notebook - notes by Riggs, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Hawaii International Film Festival program, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      featuring Color Adjustment screening
    - Color Adjustment Edit Decision List (Box 92, Folder 3)
      with floppy discs, moved to Box 093
    - Color Adjustment Edit Decision List (Deborah Hoffman) (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment American Film Institute Funding Correspondence, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Color Adjustment AFI Funding Correspondence, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Color Adjustment AFI Funding budget, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Color Adjustment AFI Funding account, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment AFI Funding checking account (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Funding Checking account Budget, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Color Adjustment California Council for the Humanities Funding, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Color Adjustment CCH Invoices, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Color Adjustment CCH Invoices, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Color Adjustment CCH Supplementary funding, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment CCH Funding Final Reports, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Color Adjustment CCH Production application, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Color Adjustment CCH application, originals (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Color Adjustment CCH checking account statements, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Color Adjustment Corporation for Public Broadcasting Funding Reports,1988-1992 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - CPB Proposal, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - CPB Contract (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - CPB Budget (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - The Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1991-92 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - The Gerbode Foundation, Correspondence, 1990-92 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - NEA, application, 1989/1990 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - NEA, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - NEA, Budget, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Funding -New York Council for the Humanities, Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - NYCH, Budget, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Color Adjustment Funding - The Rockefeller Foundation, Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Academy Award application (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - American Film Institute (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Amsterdam Internatio Documentary (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Athens (Ohio) International Film & Video Festival, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Atlanta Film & Video Festival (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Berlin Film Festival (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Black Filmworks Film & Video festival, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Black International Cinema, Berlin 1992 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Black Maria Film & Video festival (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Cleveland International Film Festival application (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Chicago International Film festival, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Dallas Video Festival, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Denver International Film Festival, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Emmy application (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - FESPACO, 1993, Festival of Pan African Film (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Film Arts Foundation, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Haifa International Film Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Hawaii International Film Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Houston International Film & Video Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Input '93 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - IDA Awards, 1991, International Documentary Association (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Independent Feature Film Market, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Jerusalem Film Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - London Film Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Los Angeles Gay & Lesbian Film & Video Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Louisville Film & Video Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Margaret Mead Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Color Adjustment Festivals - Melbourne International Film Festival, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 15)